Peter Altshuler

Product Designer, Israel

Portfolio Linkedin E-mail Phone

zenpeter.com linkedin.com/in/zenpeter zenshuler@gmail.com (058) 670-1290

Summary

Driven by logic and systematic decision-making, I have a 2+ year track record working with big companies and startups. Key achievements include creating a design system for Similarweb and contributing to the redesign of Baby.ru—the largest Eastern European website for mothers.

Experience

Product designer — Freelance

Jan 2022 - Present

Quickscore

- Designed web interfaces, mobile apps and scoreboard Uls.
- Crafted branding elements, logos, and marketing materials.
- Contributed to doubling the company's user offerings.

Baby.ru

- Contributed to a global redesign by crafting a new UI kit and design system guidance.
- Crafted 350 components for the UI kit while achieving a 25% reduction in text styles.
- I redesigned all desktop pages and created corresponding mobile versions.

UX/UI Designer — eMode

Apr 2021 — Jan 2022

- Designed various digital projects for companies and startups.
- Conducted research, crafted wireframes, mockups, and prototypes.
- Transferred design layouts to developers, actively supporting the development process.

Product Designer Intern — Similarweb

Sep 2020 — Jan 2021

- Conducted comprehensive research initiatives.
- Identified and resolved conflicts between design files and production.
- Crafted key components for a design system, laying the foundation for a global redesign.

Education

UX Design — Google Professional Certificate

Apr 2021 — Jan 2022

- Building Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes
- Conducting UX Research
- Creating High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes

Bachelor of Law — BSAU, Belarus

Oct 2016 — Dec 2019

- Communication & Negotiation: debated and defended decisions based on legal acts.
- Ethical Knowledge: acquired knowledge in user privacy, accessibility and legal compliance.
- Analytical Thinking: analyzed legal aspects using a data-driven problem-solving approach.

Bachelor of Engineering — BSAU, Belarus

Sep 2013 — Jan 2018

- Problem Solving: researched and improved real estate valuation processes in graduate work.
- Project Management: planned and executed land management projects.
- Attention to Detail: ensured engineering designs were accurate and met industry standards.

Skills & Tools

Hard skills Soft skills Tools

User Research & Analysis Problem-Solving Figma
Information Architecture Attention to Detail Adobe CS
Accessibility Storytelling Notion
Wireframing & Prototyping Active Listener Framer
Responsive design Communication & presentation HTML/CSS

esponsive design Communication & presentation HTML/C3

Languages English Hebrew Russian
Fluent Beginner Native